

Wolenberg Silva

Nationality: Brazilian (+55) 83988532566

Date of birth: 14/02/1990

Gender: Male

Email address: wolembergjp@gmail.com

Website: https://wolenbergportfolio.netlify.app/

(C) Whatsapp Messenger: +5583988532566

in LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/wolenberg-silva-31b685157/

• Address: 58066000 João Pessoa (Brazil)

ABOUT ME

I consider my self a creative and responsible professional with excellent troubleshooting skills, proficiency knowledge of software developer and exceptional comunicate skills. 8 years+ experience in improving and updating software perfomance, as well as developing new software functionalities using best pratices in applications such as Power Platform, Java Enviroment, Angular, SQL and VBA.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior System Enginner
Indra Company [30/04/2021 - Current]

City: Joao Pessoa Country: Brazil

This role is part of the Product Team Digital Enablement and is one of the professionals who do the work of delivering a potentially releasable increment of the product at the end of each sprint. Product Teams are structured and empowered by the organization to organize and manage their own work.

Task and Activies:

- $\,^\circ$ Resolve incidents opened by issuing tickets reported by users from different areas
- Application support maintained in manageable environments applying global security policies
- Monitoring application executions and usage, preventing excessive use of resources
- Architect new projects for various improvements in the work routine of the business areas.

Results:

- $\,\circ\,$ Several new projects created, optimizing automations in various aspects of the business rule.
- Report indicators for incident prevention and preventive maintenance.
- Citizen developers with self-sufficient knowledge of creating their applications, after completing the training carried out by the team.

Technologies:

Microsoft Power Platform (Power Apps , Power Automate), Microsoft Sharepoint, Microsoft Dataverse , Azure Devops, Dynamics 365, SCRUM, Kanban.

Freelancer Developer

Autonomous [01/10/2017 - 01/05/2021]

City: Joao Pessoa

Country: Brazil

Developing new features and improving perfomance from softwares, maintenance of existing applications of retail sector as core business.

Task and Activies:

- Develop applications to sustain all the intern process.
- Maintenace in existing applications, creating a new rules to optimezed the business process.
- Integrated with all kind of automation hardwares to facilited the flow of process.
- Management of databases to garanted the integrity and security of stored data.

Results:

- Created some multiple applications with capacity to do all business process and stored data with a database solid and
- Created multiple reports to bring the point of decision to the client with the results of your sales for example.
- Created APIs to easier communicate and integrated with thirds solutions.

Tecnologies:

Microsoft Power Platform (Power Apps , Power Automate), Microsoft Access (VBA), Microsoft SQL Server, Java Springbot, JavaScript , HTML, CSS, Angular

Fullstack Software Developer

Softcom Tecnologia [01/08/2010 - 01/09/2017]

City: Joao Pessoa Country: Brazil

Technical support and development to guaranteed the integrity of running applications and developer a new features for clients necessity.

Task and Acitivies:

- IT Support by helpdesk, receiving issues by phone call from general users of the software.
- External activity, coming out to the physical place to install applications, hardware's and training the new users how to make the process in the commercial app.
- Developer a new functions and features to the main application of the core business, to get the updates necessary to run the commercial software.
- Architect new and custom projects, to clients who the standard solution doesn't attend their necessities.

Results:

- Build a lot of applications from a several business areas, with focus to a retail and ecommerce solutions.
- Use of practical and modern methodologies regarding IT process management.

Tecnologies:

Microsoft Access (VBA), Microsoft SQL Server, .Net Core, XML, Firebird Database

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Graduation in mathematics

Universidade Federal da Paraiba [01/04/2017 - 01/05/2021]

Address: (Brazil)

Analysis and systems development

UNOPAR [01/02/2013 - 01/05/2014]

Address: (Brazil)

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): Portuguese

Other language(s):

English

LISTENING B2 READING B2 WRITING B2

SPOKEN PRODUCTION B2 SPOKEN INTERACTION B2

Spanish

LISTENING A2 READING A2 WRITING A2

SPOKEN PRODUCTION A2 SPOKEN INTERACTION A2

CERTIFICATIONS

Microsoft Certified: Azure Fundamentals AZ-900

[22/04/2022]

Earners of the Azure Fundamentals certification have demonstrated foundational level knowledge of cloud services and how those services are provided with Microsoft Azure.

https://www.credly.com/badges/77e5b8d2-4ff3-4f9c-b3be-41a3e92d562f

Microsoft Power Platform Fundamentals PL-900

[19/08/2021]

Earners of the Power Platform Fundamentals certification are users who aspire to improve productivity by automating business processes, analyzing data to produce business insights, and acting more effectively by creating simple app experiences.

https://www.credly.com/badges/e50eb5be-a2a2-47de-9b70-f5add0eaec43/linked in

IT Service Management Foundation

[29/12/2014]

Based on ISO/IEC 20000

ITIL V3 Foundation

Certificate in IT Service Management

DIGITAL SKILLS

Microsoft Power Platform (Power BI, Power Apps, Power Automate) / MS Power Platform (Power Apps, Power Automate) / Dynamics 365 / Azure, Azure DevOps / Azure Pipelines / SQL (MySQL) / GIT (Git Hub, Git Bash) / Microsoft Excel including VBA Macros (high proficiency)